HASAN ÇALI

• DETAILS •

Gazi Yakup Satar Street 275 Eskişehir, 26220 Turkey +905318604512 hasancali16@hotmail.com

o LINKS o

<u>Linkedin</u>

<u>Instagram</u>

SKILLS

Critical Thinking

Effective Communication

Adaptability and Flexibility

Project & Time Management

Problem Solving

• SOFTWARE •

C#

.NET Core

Angular

SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL)

HTML & CSS

Flutter

TypeScript

LANGUAGES

Turkish

English

German

PROFILE

Interested in new technologies to become a self-evolving software specialist. Recognizes the significance of following and adapting to advances. Extensive knowledge of cutting-edge development tools and techniques. Capable of managing oneself well during independent work as well as collaborating as part of a productive team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Software Developer at Alpata Software and Technologies Inc.

July 2019 — Present

- Responsible for Project Development and Support Process for 50+ clients
 Supervised long-standing problem's solutions with a 98% customer satisfaction
 score
- Developed *full-stack applications* throughout various platforms using cutting-edge industry technologies and frameworks
- Assisted in recruiting new employees to the project team and establishing an in-house R&D team. Supported the adaptation processes of team members.
- Supervised a team of 4 to devise new tools and libraries for reducing re-coding among employees with AI applications and decreased total project time to 30%
- Integrated structures such as Kubernetes, Docker to publish several APIs with .NET
 Core for the company database within R&D team
- Aided develop an innovative design template and methods using Angular for Web Projects. Pioneered the use of Flutter in mobile applications tasks

Software Developer at Freelance

January 2013 — Present

- Design, develop and support from the analysis process to the end of the project according to customer needs and the new features of the existing project
- Succeed in more than 100+ project work with 95% approval rate at first review from clients

<u>Skills:</u> C#, MVC, JQUERY, JavaScript, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, JAVA, WPF, Windows Form, MSSQL, MYSQL, DevExpress, Graylog, Traffic

Software Developer at Ceviz Software

May 2019 — August 2019

- Established corporate and e-commerce websites using several technologies and frameworks like C#, MVC, WordPress, HTML & CSS, and PHP
- Enhanced 3+ full-stack web applications to analyze and process data for international clients
- Controlled time-sensitive updates, including content revisions and database renewals

Software Developer at Designoweb Technologies

July 2018 — January 2019

 Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment

- Used front-end application tools like HTML & CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, AJAX and Jquery
- Headed of maintaining, optimizing, troubleshooting, and improving websites to the team to integrate new feature development

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Management Information Systems, Anadolu University, Distance Learning

September 2018 — Present

<u>Focus Area:</u> Data analysis, Programming Languages, Project management, and Underlying Business Theories

Associate of Science in Computer Programming, Dokuz Eylül University

September 2017 — June 2018

Graduated with High Honors

Focus Area: Algorithms & Theory, Database Systems, Programming Languages

Associate of Science in Aircraft Technology, Anadolu University

September 2015 — June 2017

Graduated with High Honors

Focus Area: Aircraft Maintenance

CERTIFICATES

Fall and Spring Semester High Honor Certificate , Dokuz Eylül University 2017 — 2018

A1 AML (Aircraft Maintenance Licence), Turkish Technic $\mathsf{July}\ 2017$

Fall and Spring Semester High Honor Certificate , Anadolu University 2016-2017

★ HOBBIES

Open-water swimming, Trekking, Off-road, Soccer